"Why do I see you everywhere?"
"Every path I tread on.."
"..keeps asking me for you."
"Why is a moment of love.."
"..more valuable than an entire life!
Why is it so, Oh Lord!"
"There's a void in my heart."
"I am lonely without you."
"I can feel your presence
everywhere...but you're nowhere."
"You're unaware..."
"You're around every bend."
"All I want to know.."
"..why did you change
like the weather."
You should spare some time..
...for something you work so hard.
At least watch what you're eating.
Good morning, dad.
Okay-
Thank you.
There's a big similarity
between medicine and marriage.
If you don't get it on time..
...it can cause great problems.
You are absolutely right.
And I want your kids..
...to call me Great grandma, not you.
Sis, she is right...get married.
I can't get married until you don't.
Did I give you all this news or not?
Himanshu Tyagi is coming.
Remember,
Himanshu Tyagi, my batch mate's Son.
I see..
He was born in London.
Thorough gentleman.
You studied with him..
You were friends, right?
Dad, I was 8 years old.
Yeah.
And he'll be staying here.
I see. - He'll stay here
until he doesn't complete his work.
I think you should go and pick him up.
Dad, please give me some time.
Please..
That's fine.
Fine.
Dad, don't do that.
No, no, no, it's okay. it's..it's..
- Dad..
No, no, it's absolutely okay.
You know something, I am stuck.
I am stuck with three women..